You have to practice a certain level of self-care, or else you will not have what you need.
Like, when we would see pictures of Martin Luther King on vacation, like, that's because, like, yes,
this man was out here marching and marching, but can he get some time in Jamaica?
Can the man go in the pool?
Yes, he needs to, because then he's got to be able to come back.
He has to restore.
He has to relax, relate, release.
All of us need to do that.
And for a lot of us, we do that by finding spaces to interact with others that are enriching versus depleting.
So here's some ways.
These are some ways in which you can be a positive conductor.
I don't mean a conductor like you are conducting an orchestra, even though in some way of a way you are.
I don't mean a conductor meaning that you are a train conductor saying, all aboard!
I mean a conductor in that you are an attractor of positivity.